<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:id="@+id/pizzaRecipeBg"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:layout_margin="12dp"
    tools:context=".PizzaRecipeActivity">

    <ImageView
        android:id="@+id/pizzaImageRecipe"
        android:layout_width="150dp"
        android:layout_height="150dp"
        android:scaleType="centerCrop"
        app:srcCompat="@drawable/marghuerita1"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"/>

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/pizzaNameRecipe"
        android:layout_width="0dp"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toEndOf="@id/pizzaImageRecipe"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="@id/pizzaImageRecipe"
        android:text="Pizza Name"
        android:textColor="@color/black"
        android:textStyle="bold"
        android:textSize="25sp"
        android:layout_marginHorizontal="4dp"/>

    <ImageView
        android:id="@+id/backButton"
        android:layout_width="50dp"
        android:layout_height="50dp"
        android:layout_margin="12dp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:srcCompat="@drawable/baseline_arrow_back_24"
        android:onClick="Back"/>

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/pizzaDescribeRecipe"
        android:layout_width="0dp"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="@id/pizzaNameRecipe"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toBottomOf="@id/pizzaNameRecipe"
        android:layout_marginHorizontal="4dp"
        android:textSize="14sp"
        android:textColor="@color/black"
        android:alpha="0.85"
        />

    <ScrollView
        android:id="@+id/ScrollView"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="0dp"
        android:layout_marginVertical="8dp"
        android:fillViewport="true"
        android:scrollbars="vertical"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toBottomOf="@id/pizzaImageRecipe"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toTopOf="@id/backButton">

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/pizzaRecipe"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:isScrollContainer="true"

            android:text="STEP 1\nFirst, make the dough. Tip the flour into a bowl and add 300ml tepid water. Mix together and set aside at room temperature for 1 hr. Dissolve the yeast in 2 tbsp water and mix this and 15g of salt through the dough. Cover with cling film and leave somewhere warm to double in size for a few hours. For a sourer flavour, leave in the fridge for at least 8 hrs and up to 24 hrs – the longer you leave it the sourer it will be.\nSTEP 2\nWhen the dough is ready, tip it onto a lightly floured surface and divide into four. Roll into balls and leave to rest, covered with a tea towel or cling film for another hour.\nSTEP 3\nNow make the tomato sauce. Drain some of the juice from the can and tip the rest into a bowl with the olive oil, oregano and a generous pinch of salt, then either scrunch everything together with your fingers for a chunky sauce or blitz with a stick blender if you want it smooth. Tie the basil stalks together, bruise with the back of a knife and place in the sauce. Leave the sauce at room temperature until needed.\nSTEP 4\nTo make the pizza, heat a grill to its highest setting and get a heavy frying pan. On a floured surface push and stretch one of the balls of dough out into a circle roughly the same size as the frying pan. Slip the round onto a floured baking sheet and top with a quarter of the sauce, a scattering of cheese, a few basil leaves and a quarter of the mozzarella.\nSTEP 5\nGet the pan very hot and carefully slide the pizza onto it. Cook for 2 mins, then put the pan under the grill for another 2 mins until the sides are puffed up and the cheese has melted. Lift onto a board, drizzle with a little olive oil if you like, then cut into wedges and serve while you make the next one."
            android:textColor="@color/black"
            android:textSize="14dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

    </ScrollView>


</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>